His mind is fading. His conscience is clear.
Memory is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Martin Campbell.
Alex, an assassin-for-hire, finds that he's become a target after he
refuses to complete a job for a dangerous criminal organization.
With the crime syndicate and FBI in hot pursuit, Alex has the skills to stay ahead, except for
one thing: he is struggling with severe memory loss, affecting his every move.
Alex must question his every action and whom he can ultimately trust.
Alex Lewis, played by Liam Neeson.
Vincent Serra, played by Guy Pearce.
Linda Amistead, played by Taj Atwal.
Hugo Marquez, played by Harold Torres.
Special Agent Gerald Nussbaum, played by Ray Fearon.
Davana Sealman, played by Monica Bellucci.
Memory is a 2022 American action thriller film starring Liam Neeson as a hitman with early
dementia who must go on the run after declining a contract on a young girl.
It is directed by Martin Campbell from a screenplay by Dario Scardapane.
It is based on the novel De Zaak Alzheimer by Jef Geeraerts and is a remake of the
novel's previous adaptation, the Belgian film  De Zaak Alzheimer.
The film also stars Guy Pearce, Monica Bellucci,
Harold Torres, Taj Atwal and Ray Fearon.
Memory was theatrically released in the United States on April 29, 2022, by Open
Road Films, and received mostly negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of assassin, alzheimer's disease, remake, assertive.
The tone is intense.